<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-07-16T12:53:36+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Other People’s Flowers</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Episode 8 - War Hero - David Calladine</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/04/11/episode-8-david-calladine.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Episode 8 - War Hero - David Calladine" /><published>2018-04-11T09:07:45+01:00</published><updated>2018-04-11T09:07:45+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/04/11/episode-8-david-calladine</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/04/11/episode-8-david-calladine.html">&lt;p&gt;This week’s episode features a short story by David Calladine about a
young man attending the funeral for a grandfather he didn’t
know. David Calladine is a former software engineer and now writer and
freelance journalist. He lives and works in the Dublin area. Other
People’s Flowers is the podcast that showcases short stories, essays,
and reportage. We’re the first podcast-based literary journal. People
hardly read journals anymore so we hope you’ll listen instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to have your work featured on the show, please send it to editor@otherpeoplesflowers.com.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This week’s episode features a short story by David Calladine about a young man attending the funeral for a grandfather he didn’t know. David Calladine is a former software engineer and now writer and freelance journalist. He lives and works in the Dublin area. Other People’s Flowers is the podcast that showcases short stories, essays, and reportage. We’re the first podcast-based literary journal. People hardly read journals anymore so we hope you’ll listen instead.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Episode 7 - Those Left Behind - Jonathan D’Arcy</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/04/04/episode-7-jonathan-darcy.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Episode 7 - Those Left Behind - Jonathan D'Arcy" /><published>2018-04-04T09:07:45+01:00</published><updated>2018-04-04T09:07:45+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/04/04/episode-7-jonathan-darcy</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/04/04/episode-7-jonathan-darcy.html">&lt;p&gt;This week’s episode features a short story by Jonathan D’Arcy about a
Classics teacher who gets left behind by society while trying to
follow him dreams. He finds himself caught up in a web of deceit and
lies that leaves him questioning many of his life choices. Jonathan
D’Arcy is an Irish writer living in the North East of England. He’s
been teaching for many years and is currently doing a PhD in
Comparative Literature. Other People’s Flowers is the podcast that
showcases short stories, essays, and reportage. We’re the first
podcast-based literary journal. People hardly read journals anymore so
we hope you’ll listen instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to have your work featured on the show, please send it to editor@otherpeoplesflowers.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This week’s episode features a short story by Jonathan D’Arcy about a Classics teacher who gets left behind by society while trying to follow him dreams. He finds himself caught up in a web of deceit and lies that leaves him questioning many of his life choices. Jonathan D’Arcy is an Irish writer living in the North East of England. He’s been teaching for many years and is currently doing a PhD in Comparative Literature. Other People’s Flowers is the podcast that showcases short stories, essays, and reportage. We’re the first podcast-based literary journal. People hardly read journals anymore so we hope you’ll listen instead.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Episode 6 - We Don’t Do Catholics Here - Jemma Prandial</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/03/28/episode-6-jemma-prandial.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Episode 6 - We Don't Do Catholics Here - Jemma Prandial" /><published>2018-03-28T09:07:45+01:00</published><updated>2018-03-28T09:07:45+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/03/28/episode-6-jemma-prandial</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/03/28/episode-6-jemma-prandial.html">&lt;p&gt;This week’s story comes from Jemma Prandial, We Don’t Do Catholics
Here. It’s about a non-religious mission in Africa and how the
volunteers there start to question their atheism when an Islamist
insurgency starts to run through the country. Jemma is a humanist and
novelist living in Kenya. She has been writing under various
pseudonyms for many years and prefers to be anonymous and
unrecognisable when writing. Other People’s Flowers is the podcast
that showcases short stories, essays, and reportage. We’re the first
podcast-based literary journal. People hardly read journals anymore so
we hope you’ll listen instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to have your work featured on the show, please send it to editor@otherpeoplesflowers.com.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This week’s story comes from Jemma Prandial, We Don’t Do Catholics Here. It’s about a non-religious mission in Africa and how the volunteers there start to question their atheism when an Islamist insurgency starts to run through the country. Jemma is a humanist and novelist living in Kenya. She has been writing under various pseudonyms for many years and prefers to be anonymous and unrecognisable when writing. Other People’s Flowers is the podcast that showcases short stories, essays, and reportage. We’re the first podcast-based literary journal. People hardly read journals anymore so we hope you’ll listen instead.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Episode 5 - Pity Friends - David Calladine</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/03/21/episode-5-david-calladine.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Episode 5 - Pity Friends - David Calladine" /><published>2018-03-21T08:07:45+00:00</published><updated>2018-03-21T08:07:45+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/03/21/episode-5-david-calladine</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/03/21/episode-5-david-calladine.html">&lt;p&gt;This week we feature a story by David Calladine, Pity Friends, about a
man visiting some of his artist friends who’ve retired from the bustle
of city life to go and live a life of art and relative poverty in
Ireland. David Calladine is a former software engineer and now writer
and freelance journalist. He lives and works in the Dublin area. Other
People’s Flowers is the podcast that showcases short stories, essays,
and reportage. We’re the first podcast-based literary journal. People
hardly read journals anymore so we hope you’ll listen instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to have your work featured on the show, please send it to editor@otherpeoplesflowers.com.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This week we feature a story by David Calladine, Pity Friends, about a man visiting some of his artist friends who’ve retired from the bustle of city life to go and live a life of art and relative poverty in Ireland. David Calladine is a former software engineer and now writer and freelance journalist. He lives and works in the Dublin area. Other People’s Flowers is the podcast that showcases short stories, essays, and reportage. We’re the first podcast-based literary journal. People hardly read journals anymore so we hope you’ll listen instead.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Episode 4 - Courting - Robert Davies</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/03/14/episode-4-robert-davies.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Episode 4 - Courting - Robert Davies" /><published>2018-03-14T08:07:45+00:00</published><updated>2018-03-14T08:07:45+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/03/14/episode-4-robert-davies</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/03/14/episode-4-robert-davies.html">&lt;p&gt;This week we feature a story by Robert Davies about the perils of
online dating. It’s a comic short story about a man who’s first
experience in the world of online dating goes horribly wrong. Robert
Davies is a standup comic and writer living in London. His work has
been featured in Granta, Paris Lit Up and The Cadaverine. He often
writes under a pseudonym. Other People’s Flowers is the podcast that
showcases short stories, essays, and reportage. We’re the first
podcast literary journal. People hardly read journals anymore so we
hope you’ll listen instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to have your work featured on the show, please send it to editor@otherpeoplesflowers.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This week we feature a story by Robert Davies about the perils of online dating. It’s a comic short story about a man who’s first experience in the world of online dating goes horribly wrong. Robert Davies is a standup comic and writer living in London. His work has been featured in Granta, Paris Lit Up and The Cadaverine. He often writes under a pseudonym. Other People’s Flowers is the podcast that showcases short stories, essays, and reportage. We’re the first podcast literary journal. People hardly read journals anymore so we hope you’ll listen instead.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Episode 3 - Inscription - Dorothy Piers</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/02/28/episode-3-dorothy-piers.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Episode 3 - Inscription - Dorothy Piers" /><published>2018-02-28T08:07:45+00:00</published><updated>2018-02-28T08:07:45+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/02/28/episode-3-dorothy-piers</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/02/28/episode-3-dorothy-piers.html">&lt;p&gt;This week we feature a story by Dorothy Piers, Inscription. It’s about
someone who finds an inscription in the front of a book by W. Somerset
Maugham and imagines who would throw away a book with an inscription
in it and for what reason. Dorothy is a writer and illustrator living
in North London. Other than her cats, writing is her great passion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to have your work featured on the show, please send it to editor@otherpeoplesflowers.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This week we feature a story by Dorothy Piers, Inscription. It’s about someone who finds an inscription in the front of a book by W. Somerset Maugham and imagines who would throw away a book with an inscription in it and for what reason. Dorothy is a writer and illustrator living in North London. Other than her cats, writing is her great passion.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Episode 2 - Allemande Grave - Daniel Richards</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/02/28/episode-2-allemande-grave-daniel-richards.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Episode 2 - Allemande Grave - Daniel Richards" /><published>2018-02-28T08:07:45+00:00</published><updated>2018-02-28T08:07:45+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/02/28/episode-2-allemande-grave-daniel-richards</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/02/28/episode-2-allemande-grave-daniel-richards.html">&lt;p&gt;This episode features a story, Allemande Grave, by Daniel Richards. A
nightwatchman in a factory hears some mysterious music and goes to
investigate. Daniel Richards is a writer and artist living in
Manchester in the UK. His work explores the effects of urban
environments on people and the ways in which our lives are twisted by
increasingly surreal landscapes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to have your work featured on the show, please send it to editor@otherpeoplesflowers.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This episode features a story, Allemande Grave, by Daniel Richards. A nightwatchman in a factory hears some mysterious music and goes to investigate. Daniel Richards is a writer and artist living in Manchester in the UK. His work explores the effects of urban environments on people and the ways in which our lives are twisted by increasingly surreal landscapes.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Episode 1 - Just Once in the Moonlight</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/02/17/episode-1-ayunda-dlamani.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Episode 1 - Just Once in the Moonlight" /><published>2018-02-17T08:07:45+00:00</published><updated>2018-02-17T08:07:45+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/02/17/episode-1-ayunda-dlamani</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/episodes/2018/02/17/episode-1-ayunda-dlamani.html">&lt;p&gt;This episode we’re featuring a story by Ayunda Dlamini about a failed
romance in Africa. Ayunda is a novelist and writer who moved to the UK
from Swaziland in 2010, and has been writing on a number of
topics. His main interested include post-colonial literature and the
world’s changing relationship with Africa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to have your work featured, please send it to editor@otherpeoplesflowers.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This episode we’re featuring a story by Ayunda Dlamini about a failed romance in Africa. Ayunda is a novelist and writer who moved to the UK from Swaziland in 2010, and has been writing on a number of topics. His main interested include post-colonial literature and the world’s changing relationship with Africa.</summary></entry></feed>